(Sheldon:)Does he provide her
with health insurance?
(Leonard:)No.
(Leonard:)Look, imagine you maintained a friendship
with someone you had sex with...
(Leonard:)...but you were free to date
whoever you wanted.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, I can't imagine any of that.
All right, back to the game.
(Sheldon:)I believe it's my turn.
(Sheldon:)You may begin your questions
whenever you're ready.
(Raj:)Are you Spock?
(Sheldon:)I don't like this game.
(Howard:)So where were we?
- Aren't you leaving for your booty call?
- No, it was something else.
(Howard:)Why does everything
have to be about sex with you? Come on.
Whose turn is it?
- We're up to you.
HOWARD: Great.
(Howard:)- Just start.
- Okay, let's see.
(Leonard:)Are you from a TV series?
(Howard:)She dumped me.
[CRYING]
(Sheldon:)I bet he's someone from Babylon 5.
We're never gonna get it.